You think I'm unshoured and greasy, don't you?
You should be ashamed of yourself, that's pathetic.
This is called acting.
I am simply playing a character that is a slimy, greasy caveman.
It's method acting.
You swine.
You wouldn't know anything of it, would you?
With your ignorance out of the way in this myth fully busted and debunked,
I'd like to proceed with the video topic if you don't mind,
which is of course more Pokemon card thieves.
I literally caught somebody in 4k,
stealing a charizard from my booth at a card show.
So let's do a play by play.
The card in question is a 25th anniversary celebrations charizard.
But let's start out by actually locating the card.
I don't even know how many videos I have at this point covering Pokemon card thieves.
This has to be one of the most commonly stolen items.
Like what else would even be close?
Fones?
Maybe?
Like perhaps?
But I don't even know, because phones, like nowadays, are like often locked down.
And people know that if you just steal a display phone, you can't do shit with it.
You can maybe shove it up your ass and that's about it.
So like I can't even think of something else that would be stolen.
That would be stolen as frequently as Pokemon cards have been over the last year.
Because there's at least like five or six robberies a week that we know of with video evidence
of people stealing Pokemon cards.
And here we can see one of the guys at the show pick it up to have a look at it.
We can see put the charizard card right down at the front of my table.
It's in the danger zone.
And now moments later, let me introduce you to Jamie.
Now between the face tat and the high viz,
Pro's not helping himself go incognito on this one.
We see Jamie walk past the charizard card and quite clearly lock eyes with it.
I saw a lot of super sleuths in the comments,
debating whether or not that first guy was in on this.
And I will admit, it is odd that he would pick up the charizard and then put it so far away
from the place that he got it from.
And especially at a card show, most people there probably are somewhat knowledgeable on cards.
He would definitely know that putting a card on the edge of the table there,
that's like showing the waters around sharks.
That is a disaster waiting to happen.
Like I feel like there is merit to the idea that he could have known this guy.
And this was like a planned thing.
But the uploader shoots that theory down by mentioning that he actually knows that first guy
personally and he was interested in buying that card.
The reason he had to step away was because something outside of that needed his tending to.
So we left to go do that and then came back to buy the card.
And it was gone.
And he said at no point to those two ever interact or anything.
So I would take his word that the first guy probably wasn't in on it.
Plus, I also feel like with the way that the card got stolen,
this probably wasn't a multi-person operation.
This guy right here wearing like the most obvious attire.
But he literally is wearing a fucking fortnight skin to stand out in front of as many people as possible.
He is literally wearing accoutrements that are designed so you can see them in the dark.
He is actually, it's like he's putting up a whole beacon.
Like he's giving everyone a fucking UAV so they can constantly find him in the crowd.
And he is going to steal this card in the most neandertholic way possible.
He just grabs it.
And with shaky hands, he even goes in for a little cheeky touch.
Now with phone in the left hand of the ready, it's incredible how quickly he's locked in on swiping this thing.
Try and act a little non-shelon, has a little gander in the case and then looks straight back at me
to see whether I'm at all paying attention.
What I'm not, my camera definitely is.
And here we can see that Jamie's specced all of his skill points into stealth and
thievery because look at this cheeky maneuver.
Bang and the card is gone and good at perfectly so we can see it on the bottom of his phone.
Right here.
That's about as simple as it gets right there.
I just don't believe the first guy was in on it here.
I don't think this was premeditated and planned.
It's clearly not some oceans 11 style heist.
This guy just sees the card at the edge of the table.
He like caresses it once or twice, honks on it like a pair of boobies and then he puts his phone
on top of it and grabs it.
And that's it.
And you can clearly see that he grabs the card and even flashes the camera.
Now Jamie's misplayed this a lot as his mum or I don't know I'm just assuming it could be his partner.
Has looked over at the exact right time.
I don't know.
I'm pretty good at lip reading and I'm pretty sure she says,
yeah man, ringy, she's going to be the channel.
He makes fun of this lady at the end here and makes a joke out of it,
assuming that she knows what just happened.
I'm not convinced she does.
Like her turning around and then seeing this guy,
I don't think immediately would raise red flags that she must have known that he stole that
Pokemon card because he does have the Pokemon card under his phone.
We as the viewers can clearly recognize that the card has just been stolen.
He's not a good thief by any means.
He's like the fucking wet bandits if they win around banging trash can't together to make
as much noise as possible during burglaries.
Like he is bad at it, sure.
But to someone that's on that side where she is from that angle,
how the fuck would she see that card?
How would she know?
Unless she has Superman's X-ray vision,
there's no way she's going to notice that he's just stole a Pokemon card under that phone.
Unless she uses mom and just expects her son to hold on a lip and get fart.
I had to rip some ass right there.
And just expecting her son to be stealing Pokemon cards.
Which I guess is possible.
Like yeah, there's a chance she knew.
And she does say something that seems to be targeted towards this guy.
But I don't know what it is.
And I just find it hard to believe that somehow she saw that happen.
Because it looks like she was looking in the other direction when he made his big move there.
Anyway, I want to show you another Pokemon thief.
So that's how it's going to be.
This is the hotspot for stealing Pokemon cards.
I have seen so, so, so many clips now of people just going into card shops and just
not even trying to hide it.
Just stealing cards and walking out.
There have been so many videos like this.
But this one's the newest that I've seen.
So I figured might as well show this.
This guy with no shame at all.
He's looking at cards right now.
He's got his phone out.
And I guess maybe trying to price check it or something.
And then he just makes his move.
His move being a bumbling off that just puts the cards in his pocket and instantly gets caught.
Have fun.
All right, well, thank you.
Alright, we'll take a look at the first game and we'll just kind of get the third box遅 işte.
Any angry about anything else?
This guy just stole Pokemon cards while wearing his company shirt.
He's literally wearing his job uniform while doing this.
Again, the shamelessness of stealing Pokemon cards here is shocking.
These are people that are trying to be stealthy about it.
Like all he does is he puts the cards in his pocket.
Then he instantly gets caught doing it because it's just so clear.
Plus he asked to see those cards.
Did he just think that these are NPCs in a video game who just forgot that they did that?
It's been 15 seconds.
Okay, I forgot what I was doing.
It must have been the wind.
How did he think he would possibly get away with that?
When he puts the cards back, they're going to notice that it's missing a few.
The natural conclusion would be like, oh, where did those cards go?
Must have been the wind and fell to the back rooms, I guess.
It's craziness.
Even if they didn't catch him in the act, when he went and slapped the cards down, I'm
sure the workers would have been like, where are the other cards?
And then what?
Was he planning to run away?
But she happened to see it happen, has the camera pulled up and he instantly like, you
know, caught me.
You did a good job.
You'll always remember this as the day you caught Captain Jack Sparrow.
It's craziness.
And this isn't even like the most egregious one.
I've seen videos of people just reaching over the counter while the worker turns around
briefly to just steal cards out of the display and then they stand there.
And then obviously the worker is going to notice that it's missing cards in the fucking
display.
It is crazy how out of control stealing Pokemon cards is and just how blatant people are
with it.
Because I think they're just so confident that even if they get caught, there's no real
repercussions.
Because in cases like with the charizard, I looked it up, near meant that card goes for
like a hundred forty bucks.
I think people just feel really confident stealing this because they, A, don't expect people
to pursue it very hard.
B, even if they do, the police probably won't do very much about it because it's not
like extremely expensive.
They're just stealing a couple of cards here and there and see they think if they steal
these, they can immediately turn around and sell it for a ton of money which you can't.
That is just a terrible idea to even steal these in the first place trying to make money
off that shit.
It is so out of control.
It is nuts with every, not just Pokemon.
Everything in the TCG space right now is just bonkers.
Anyway, I just wanted to show you these two instances of stealing cards really poorly.
That's about it.